(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
公演ハッシュタグ #MGO_LIVE
Performance hashtag #MGO_LIVE
○ スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OK
○ SNSでの感想投稿OK
○ Posting screenshots on SNS is allowed.
○ Posting impressions on SNS is allowed.
× 録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
× Recording, filming, and unauthorized re-streaming are strictly prohibited.
MGO
Welcome to Midnight Mission.
Enjoy the show.
Midnight Mission.
Welcome to Midnight Mission.
Enjoy the show.
Midnight Mission.
Welcome to Midnight Mission.
Enjoy the show.
Midnight Mission.
MGO
Welcome to Midnight Mission.
Enjoy the show.
Midnight Mission.
Welcome to Midnight Mission.
Enjoy the show.
Midnight Mission.
Welcome to Midnight Mission.
Enjoy the show.
MGO
Midnight Mission.
Welcome to Midnight Mission.
Enjoy the show.
Midnight Mission.
Welcome to Midnight Mission.
Enjoy the show.
Midnight Mission.
Welcome to Midnight Mission.
Enjoy the show.
MGO
Midnight Mission.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while until the performance starts.
公演ハッシュタグ #MGO_LIVE
Event Hashtag: #MGO_LIVE
○ スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード・投稿OK
× 録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
○ Screenshots and SNS posts are allowed.
× Recording, filming, and unauthorized distribution are strictly prohibited.
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1ST LIVE Midnight Mission
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The performance will begin shortly. Please wait a moment.
公演ハッシュタグ #MGO_LIVE
Performance hashtag: #MGO_LIVE
〇 スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OK SNSでの感想投稿OK
○ Screenshots and SNS posts are welcome.
× 録音、録画、ミラー配信や
× Recording, filming, and
違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
unauthorized distribution are strictly prohibited.
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st LIVE「Midnight Mission」へご来場いただきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for coming to Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st LIVE "Midnight Mission."
開演に先立ちまして、ご来場のお客様にご案内、およびご注意を申し上げます。
Before the show begins, we have some information and precautions for the audience.
公演中の写真撮影、録音、録画はお断りさせていただきます。
Photography, recording, and filming during the performance are prohibited.
携帯電話は音の出ないよう、電源をお切りいただくか、マナーモードに設定をいただけますよう、お願い申し上げます。
Please turn off your mobile phones or set them to silent mode to prevent any noise.
公演中、お席前後への駆け寄り等、他のお客様のご迷惑となるような行為は、一切お控えください。
During the performance, please refrain from running to the front or back of the seats or any other behavior that may inconvenience others.
本公演は全席スタンディングでの公演となります。
This performance is an all-standing show.
会場内で万が一、気分が悪くなった方がいらっしゃいましたら、お近くの係員までお声がけください。
If you feel unwell within the venue, please speak to a nearby staff member.
また、こまめな水分補給も行っていただきますよう、お願い申し上げます。
Also, please remember to hydrate frequently.
本日は客席内に配信用のカメラを設置しております。
Cameras for live streaming are installed in the audience area today.
客席内が映る可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please be aware that the audience area may be shown on camera.
演出の都合により、開演すると場内のすべての避難誘導灯が消灯いたします。
For production reasons, all emergency exit lights in the venue will be turned off once the show starts.
避難が必要となった場合には、すべての避難誘導灯が直ちに点灯いたします。
In the event that an evacuation is necessary, all emergency exit lights will be turned on immediately.
係員の指示があるまで、慌てずに、ご自身のお席で待機いただきますよう、お願い申し上げます。
Please remain calm and wait at your place until you receive instructions from the staff.
まもなく開演いたします。お済みでないお客様は、お早めに場内へお入りください。
The show will start shortly. If you haven't entered yet, please do so as soon as possible.
見下ろした 天井の隙間
The gap in the ceiling I looked down upon
見下ろした 三日月も笑って
Even the crescent moon I looked down upon is laughing
不穏げなセンチメントだって
Even unsettling sentiments
包み隠すネイビーブルー
Are wrapped and hidden in navy blue
さあ 終わらない
Come on, this never-ending...
夜をあげる
...night is for you.
終わらない
Never-ending
夜をあげる さあ
The night is for you, come on
STARTING A MISSION
NEVER ENDING MIDNIGHT
EXPLOSION
WARNING
終わらない
Never-ending
夜をあげる
This night is for you.
ESCAPING
君だけの
Just for you,
夜をあげる
I'll give you this night.
静寂を切り裂いた号砲
The signal flare that tore through the silence
幕が開いていく
The curtain begins to rise.
Midnight Mission
MOVING
声が聞こえてる 聞こえてる
I can hear your voice, I can hear it
声が聞こえてる 向こうから
I can hear your voice from the other side
頭に響いた 洗辿って
It echoed in my head, tracing the trail
今
Now
空は騒いでる 騒いでる
The sky is making a noise, making a noise
未確認飛行 ランページ
Unidentified flying rampage
アレグロ背負って 駆け出して
Carrying allegro on your back, start running
さあ
Now
WARNING
SOS SOS SOS SOS SOS SOS SOS SOS
警報 全方位 潜行 電波網
Alarm, all directions, underwater radio network
向かっている 向かっている
Heading there, heading there
さあ
Now
SOS SOS SOS SOS SOS SOS SOS SOS
警報 全方位 絶叫 電波網
Alarm, all directions, screaming radio network
歌っていけ 歌っていけ
Keep singing, keep singing
RECEIVING SOS
SYSTEM STABLE
波に呑まれるな 呑まれるな
Don't be swallowed by the waves, don't be swallowed
波に呑まれるな 声出せ
Don't be swallowed by the waves, let your voice out
彼方で光った ポイントに向かって
Towards the point that flashed in the distance
今
Now
空は騒いでる 騒いでる
The sky is making a noise, making a noise
APPROACHING
規格外規模 トランジション
Out-of-standard scale transition
アレグロ背負って 撒き出して
Carrying allegro on your back, start rolling out
さあ
Now
僕の番だ
It's my turn
WARNING
SOS SOS SOS SOS SOS SOS SOS SOS
警報 全方位 潜行 電波網
Alarm, all directions, underwater radio network
向かっている 向かっている
Heading there, heading there
さあ
Now
RECEIVING SOS
SOS SOS SOS SOS SOS SOS SOS SOS
警報 全方位 絶体絶命
Alarm, all directions, desperate situation
歌っていけ 歌っていけ
Keep singing, keep singing
抗っていけ 笑ったままで
Keep resisting, with a smile
SYSTEM STABLE
歌っていけ
Keep singing
さあ
Now
ありがとう
Thank you
搭乗したフライトの雑踏 まるでディストピアのように留まって
The crowd on the flight I boarded, stayed just like a dystopia
ご自由のネオンのマーケット
In the free neon market
問題はそこ現行いたして 秘密裏にそっと打ち負かして
The problem is there, act now, secretly and gently defeat it
この街が今日のターゲット
This city is today's target
シニカルな逆光 意外なこの人工プラットフォーム
Cynical backlighting, this unexpected artificial platform
皮肉なこの夜行 I love that déjà vu
This ironic night travel, I love that déjà vu
不自然な呼吸も戻して 刻んだプライスもそっとかわして
Restoring unnatural breathing, gently dodging the carved price
審美なダイスはそこで スポイルであり承知のさ乱れ
The aesthetic dice are there, a spoil and a known disorder
さぁ始めようか
Well, shall we begin?
しらじらしいポーカー
Shameless poker
終わりのない夜を明ける
Opening the endless night
あいつの正体秘密暴きあって 不意なレスポンス
Revealing that guy's true identity secret, an unexpected response
最高のスマイルを見透かせて Hello Upset!
Seeing through the best smile, Hello Upset!
撃ち抜いた成果の身をもって 交わして繋いできていたって
With the body of the shot-down result, exchanging and connecting
カオティックな音にのせて
Setting it to a chaotic sound
あいつの正体秘密暴きあっても アイロニーなテンポで
Even if revealing his identity, with an ironic tempo
錆び付いていたって僕の共犯者と話して
Even if rusted, talk with my accomplice
撃ち抜いた成果の身を泳いで 僕のベストフェイクトな
Swimming in the body of the shot-down result, my best faked
カオティックな音で踊れ
Dance to the chaotic sound
さぁハイになって
Well, get high
さぁちょっぴり空虚を孕んで この街の憂いをそっと飛ばして
Well, pregnant with a little emptiness, gently blow away the town's sorrow
右には罠 左が裏で
A trap on the right, the back on the left
既知の耳鳴りスリストーミーに 盲信して解いて
Known tinnitus three stormy, blindly believe and solve it
不意に狂ったチューニング
An unexpectedly crazy tuning
ロード・オフ・十分 凍えてたずっと意識下にレトロな証拠不法
Road of enough, frozen all the time, retro evidence illegal under consciousness
拾えるわけじゃないの
It's not that I can pick it up
ロード・ラスト・十分 証拠までも心臓スナイパー
Road, last, enough, heart sniper to the evidence
この知らせでいいさ 合い待ったって承知のさ乱れ
This news is fine, meeting each other and well-known disorder
さぁどうしようか
Well, what shall we do?
負けず嫌いのポーカー
Stubborn poker
それでもまだ笑ったままで
Still with a smile
あいつの正体秘密暴きあって 終わったはずだったったって
Revealing his identity, it was supposed to be over
最高のスマイルを見透かせて Hello Upset!
Seeing through the best smile, Hello Upset!
迎撃した体躯を身をもって かざして繋いできていたって
With the body of the intercepted torso, holding it up and connecting
カオティックな音にのせて
Setting it to a chaotic sound
あいつをもう一個攫うよ 喝采回顧録で
I'll kidnap him one more time, in the applause memoir
錆び付いていたって僕の共犯者の手話して
Even if rusted, using the sign language of my accomplice
迎撃した体躯を泳いで 僕のベストフェイクトな
Swimming in the intercepted torso, my best faked
カオティックな音で踊れ
Dance to the chaotic sound
さぁハイになって
Well, get high
俳優面して踊れ走って
Acting and dancing, running
カオティックな音で 踊れ
With a chaotic sound, dance
さぁハイになって
Well, get high
カバンタイトルモノの雑踏
Crowd of things titled bags
聞き慣れたデジャヴ
The familiar déjà vu
優越の速いシグナル追加
Adding a signal of fast superiority
あいつはキックスタート
He's a kickstart
スパンコード待ってられんを撃たれたリピート
Can't wait for spancode, the shot repeat
スパンコードは感情、視界も歪むオーパス
Spancode is emotion, opus that distorts the vision
曖昧なビート少じゃないな 秘密のフェンダー・アップファイア
It's not a little ambiguous beat, secret Fender upfire
槍の雨は交わすは今夜の兵
The spear rain is what the soldiers of tonight exchange
街はオールナイター 昨夜は僕らレッドライナー
The city's an all-nighter, tonight we're red-liners
加速してもっとライトスピーダー リードを突破して
Accelerate even more, light speeder, breaking through the lead
こっちおいで 追いつけないぜ 粒鳴らして撒いたチェイサー
Come over here, you can't catch up, scattered the chaser with a snap
狂ってるさ フェイズシフター You give up のイグナイター
Going crazy, phase shifter, an igniter of "you give up"
嘘つきさ ソロンでサード ラフチャーズパレード
Liar, at Solon the third, laughter's parade
刃のトリック オフの結界から ストラックアウト・パレード
Blade trick, from the off-barrier, strike out parade
まだ不透明なスタンスに セカンド どこ見てんだ ラミテンダー
Still in an opaque stance, second, where are you looking, love me tender?
指を鳴らして愛して 今夜はハイ
Snap your fingers and love me, tonight's high
こっちおいで 追いつけないぜ この速度でライドバイバイ
Come over here, you can't catch up, ride bye-bye at this speed
めくってあんなに見えた You give up のイグナイター
Flipped over, you saw so much, an igniter of "you give up"
夢を見てる時が一番ダンスでやめた
The time when I'm dreaming is the best dance, I quit
曲がったまま行け目指せマッハ
Keep it bent, go, aim for Mach
背中にドロップしたムービーサービス
The movie service dropped on my back
焦りなちょっとベンチレーション ぶっ千切ってバックファイヤー
Hurry up a little, ventilation, tear it apart and backfire
限界突破 インジケーター 止まってらんないの
Breaking through the limits, indicator, I can't stay still
街はオールナイター 昨夜は僕らレッドライナー
The city's an all-nighter, tonight we're red-liners
踊ってたいな それでいいんだ 孤独をジャンプして
I want to keep dancing, that's fine, jump over the loneliness
こっちおいで 追いつけないぜ ぶっ飛ばすぜ テールライト
Come over here, you can't catch up, I'll blast past you, tail lights
走ってパスバイ 爆増飛ばす ボートのビッグバン
Run past, explosively speeding, the boat's big bang
You give up のイグナイター
An igniter of "you give up"
Midnight Grand Orchestra です。よろしく。
We are Midnight Grand Orchestra. Nice to meet you.
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1ST LIVE
Midnight Mission
2024.2.20 (火)
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1ST LIVE
Midnight Mission
Feb 20, 2024 (Tue)
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1ST LIVE
Midnight Mission
2024.2.20 (火)
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1ST LIVE
Midnight Mission
Feb 20, 2024 (Tue)
Streaming Ticket
マルチアングルカメラ＋定点カメラ　¥8,500
マルチアングルカメラ only ¥6,500
Streaming Ticket
Multi-angle + Fixed Camera: ¥8,500
Multi-angle Camera Only: ¥6,500
チケット販売期間
2024.1.20 (土) 20:00 〜 3.12 (火) 23:59
配信プラットフォーム — SPWN
Ticket Sales Period
Jan 20, 2024 (Sat) 20:00 – Mar 12 (Tue) 23:59
Platform: SPWN
アーカイブ視聴期間
2024.3.13 (水) 23:59 まで
Archive Viewing Period
Until Mar 13, 2024 (Wed) 23:59
LIVEの続きはSPWNで販売中のStreaming Ticketで配信！ YouTube概要欄に記載のリンクをCheck! ▼
The rest of the LIVE is streaming on SPWN! Check the link in the YouTube description! ▼
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1ST LIVE "Midnight Mission"
2024.2.20 (火)
2024.2.20 (Tue)
LIVEの続きはSPWNで販売中のStreaming Ticketで配信！
The rest of the LIVE is being streamed via Streaming Tickets on sale at SPWN!
YouTube概要欄に記載のリンクをCheck！
Check the link in the YouTube description!